→ KRISTINA MARIE LAGASCA →

CONTACT

kristinalagasca@gmail.com

kristinalagasca.com

PROFILE

Dedicated individual looking for an opportunity to contribute many years of customer service experience, while utilizing technical knowledge from bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Information Security. Team player with strong technical proficiency and commitment to excellence, possessing strong skills in detail-orientation, communication, and problem-solving.

SKILLS

- ° C++, PYTHON, HTML5, CSS
- DETAIL-ORIENTED
- FRENCH 2+, CHINESE 1 (SELF-ASSESSED
- PUBLIC SPEAKING
- SALES/CUSTOMER SERVICE
- OFFICE 365 WORD, POWERPOINT, EXCEL, ONENOTE, ONEDRIVE, SHAREPOINT, POWER BI

EDUCATION

Molloy College

Sept 2013 - May 2015

Bachelor of Science – BS, Biology (Pre-Medicine) Minor in Chemistry and Mathematics

John Jay College of Criminal Justice CUNY

Aug 2015 - May 2019

Bachelor of Science – BS, Computer Science and Information Security

EXPERIENCE

Presage Security

Oct 2020 - Present

- PROFICIENCY IN PYTHON PROGRAMMING
- UNDERSTANDING MACHINE LEARNING TECHNIQUES AND ALGORITHMS
- EXPERIENCE IN AMAZON WEB SERVICES

Pride Resource Partners LLC

Dec 2019 – Oct 2020

- PROVIDING IPAD TECHNICAL SUPPORT TO FIELD CONSTRUCTION ADVISORS
 AND QUALIFIED ELECTRICAL WORKERS IN THE FIELD AND THE OFFICE
- WORKING WITH PROJECT TEAMS AND SHAREPOINT ADMINISTRATORS TO DELIVER TRAININGS FOR SHAREPOINT END-USERS ABOUT THE PROCESSES/POLICIES OF THE PROJECT SITE
- ASSISTING WITH THE CREATION AND MAINTENANCE OF TRAINING
 RESOURCES/STANDARD OPERATING PROCEDURES FOR THE PROJECT SITE
- KEEPING AND MAINTAINING RECORDS OF END-USERS THAT WERE TRAINED.

Microsoft

Jun 2016 – Dec 2019

- HELPING CUSTOMERS DISCOVER, BUY, USE, AND LOVE MICROSOFT TECHNOLOGY SOLUTION AND SERVICES THAT MEET AND EXCEED THEIR INDIVIDUAL EXPECTATIONS
- PROVIDE WORLD-CLASS CUSTOMER SERVICE TO THE CUSTOMERS AND HELP THEM SEE WHAT IS POSSIBLE WITH TECHNOLOGY, ULTIMATELY EMPOWERING THEM TO ACHIEVE MORE
- TEACH HOUR OF CODE AND STEM WORKSHOPS, FOR CHILDREN, THROUGH NUMEROUS WAYS & PROVIDE A FUN EXPERIENCE FOR THEM THROUGHOUT THE CLASS SO THAT YOUNGER GENERATIONS ARE INSPIRED TO HAVE A FUTURE CAREER IN STEM